Problem Statement

You are going to travel in ByteLand. ByteLand is in the form of a rectangular grid with N rows and M columns. Each grid square is a city. You have to travel from City(1, 1) to City(N, M). City(I, J) represents the city located at the Ith row and the Jth column. You arrive in a new city every day and stay in a hotel at night. There are A(I, J) hotels in City(I, J), and you can stay at any one of them.

If you are in City(I, J), you can travel to any City(I+x, J+y) where:

1) x>0 and x=y 
or
2) x=0 and y>0 
or
3) x>0 and y=0 

Your task: Calculate the number of different ways to book hotels while travelling from City(1, 1) to City(N, M). This number can be quite large, so calculate it modulo 1000000007.

The time limit for Python2, Python3 and Ruby have been changed to 13 seconds and for all other languages the timit limit is standard, have a look at EnvironmentPage for details.

Constraints :

1≤N≤2500
1≤M≤2500
0≤A(I,J)≤9
Input Format

The first line contains two space-separated integers N and M.
The next N lines each contain M numbers separated by a space. 
The Jth value in the Ith line denotes A(I,J) i.e. the number of hotels in City(I,J).

Output Format

Print the number of different ways to book hotels while travelling from City(1,1) to City(N,M) modulo 1000000007.

Sample Input

2 2
1 2
0 1
Sample Output

3
Explanation

There are 3 different ways of booking hotels in the 2 x 2 grid:
1) From City(1,1)'s only hotel to City(2,2)'s only hotel.
2) From City(1,1)'s only hotel to City(1,2)'s first hotel and then to City(2,2)'s only hotel.
3) From City(1,1)'s only hotel to City(1,2)'s second hotel and then to City(2,2)'s only hotel.