Problem Statement

You are given an array of N integers. You must find how many consecutive subsequences of this array have greater Or based sum than K1 and have greater Xor based sum than K2.

The Or based sum of an array is the sum of all pairs' results when you bitwise or those two numbers in pairs.

The Xor based sum of an array is the sum of all pairs' results when you bitwise xor those two numbers in pairs.

The time limits of C/C++ - 1sec, Java- 3sec, C# - 2sec and for all other languages the timit limit is standard, have a look at Environment Page for details.

Constraints 
3≤N≤2×105 
1≤Ai≤106 
1≤K1,K2≤1018
Input Format

The first line of input contains 3 integers: N, denoting the length of the array, K1 and K2 respectively. 
The second line contains N space separated integers denoting the elements of the array, A1,A2,...,AN.

Output Format

You need to print the number of consecutive subsequences that have greater Or based sum than K1 and have greater Xor based sum than K2 on a single line.

Sample Input

7 15 20
2 5 4 9 7 6 3
Sample Output

13
Explanation

A subsequence with the indices between 2 and 4 that satisfies our conditions: 
(5|4)+(5|9)+(4|9)=>5+13+13=31 ( 31 is greater than K1 ) 
(5 ^ 4)+(5 ^ 9)+(4 ^ 9)=>1+12+13=26 ( 26 is greater than K2 )

There are 12 more consecutive subsequences that satisfy our conditions like this one.