Problem Statement

The Snapdeal delivery people ride bikes to deliver products to various people around the city. There are N delivery people numbered 1 through N, and M bikes numbered 1 through M. Delivery person x has strength S[x], and bike y has quality Q[y]. 
We know each delivery person's opinion of each bike. OP[x][y] is "Y" if delivery person x likes the bike y, else OP[x][y] is "N". 

The delivery person will start riding if, and only if, they have a bike that they like. This is always possible. The manager at Snapdeal wants to calculate the minimum and maximum possible team power. The team power is the sum of each delivery person's powers. The power of a delivery person x is S[x]∗Q[y] if the delivery person x is riding bike y. Help the manager calculate the minimum and maximum team power possible.

Constraints

1≤N≤M≤20
1≤S[x]≤1000
1≤Q[y]≤1000

Input Format

The first line will contain two integers N and M.
The second line will contain N integers, denoting the array S.
The third line will contain M integers, denoting the array Q.
The next N lines will contain M characters. The character in xth row and yth column denotes OP[x][y].

Output Format

Print two integers on a single line separated by a space, the minimum and maximum possible power of the delivery team, respectively.

Sample Input

2 3
1 5
1 5 5
NYY
YYN
Sample Output

10 30
Explanation

The minimum power possible is, when delivery person 1 has bike 2, and delivery person 2 has bike 1. Calculation: 1∗5+5∗1=10
The maximum power possible is, when delivery person 1 has bike 3, and delivery person 2 has bike 2. Calculation: 1∗5+5∗5=30